Guide to the Meyer Lissner Papers, 1903-1923 (inclusive), 1910-1920 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
- AS - AV
  - Republican State Cent. Com. - Calif. - L.A. 1910, 11, 16, 17M. Lissner, chairman., st. Charles R. Defrick, sec.; st. Raymond Benjamin asst. to chrmn.; s. A. H. Naftzger, v-chairman.; Joe S. Crail, chairman, campaign cam.; members, Marshall Stunsen, A Russ Avery; A.J. Wallace
  - Republican St. Cent. Com.- Calif., So. Div. - L.A. 1918, 20s. Mary E. Smith, sec.; John T. Cooper, vice-chrmn., Joe S. Crail, chairman.
  - Republican State Convention - Calif. - Sacramento 1916 s. Lee Gephant, sec.
  - Republican Ways & Means Com. of So. Cal. - L.A. 1920s. Roy C. Seeley, chairman. L.A. Com.;? mems: Harry Chandler, E.P. Clark - chairman. Advisory Com. of Nat'l Ways & Means Com. for L.A.
  - Reynolds, James Bronson - Glendale 1920,North Haven, Conn. 1921
  - Reynolds & Van Nuys Co. - Pasadena 1916, 17s. I. J. Reynolds, pres.
  - Republican State Campaign 1910 -material (news releases) from the Press Bureau, some with covering letters, in order of mailing date
  - Rhoades, Nelson O. - L.A Mexico City 1917, 20partner of James R. Garfield - Mexican counselor
  - * Rice, Phillip Hallowell - Santa Barbara 1913, 16chrmn. Santa B. Co. Repub. Progr. Co Cent. Com., real est.
  - * Richardson, Friend William - Berkeley 1911 - 1913ed. & mgr. Berkeley Daily Gazet supt. Calif. Dept. of State Printing
  - Richberg, Donald R. - Chicago 1916, 20law partner of Harold Ickes
  - Ridgeway, Thomas C. - L.A. 1915, 19
  - * Riley, Ray. L. - Colton, Cal. 1912, 13, 14, 17, 19Colton Pharmacy, Riley the Druggs San Bernardine Co. Supervisor
  - Rinehart, Robert E. - L.A. 1912genl. mgr. L.A. Municipal News
  - * Rising, Harry. P. - San Diego Escendide, Cal. 1914, 15, 19publr Escondide Advance Saturday Telegram, Sunday Telegram (S. Diego)
  - Ritter, William E. - Mt. Palemar 1908,La Jolla 1912Scripps Institute
  - Robbins, Emily F. - N.Y. 1912exec. sec. Com. of 100 on Nat'l Health
  - Roberts, C. Wesley - L.A. 1908, 12
  - * Roberts, E.D. - San Bernardino 1907, 08, 10 - 12pres. S. Ber. Nat'l Bank Calif. State Treasurer
  - Roberts, W.A. - L.A. 1912
  - Robinson, Walter H. - S.F. 1911, 12atty
  - * Rolph, James, Jr. - S.F. 1912mayor L.A. ? 1917, (1)
  - ? Rooseboom, M. P. - The Hague, Holland n.d.(see Pinchot corresp.)
  - ? Roosevelt, George Emlen - Tacoma, La Grande, Ore. Wn. 1912
  - Roosevelt, Philip J. - N.Y. 1912?Progressive Nat'l Com.
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, Jr. - N.Y. S.F. 1911, 13, 19
  - Robinson, Leo S. - S.F. Alameda 1910-13, 17controller Panama - Pacific International; Pacific Outlook & proposal California Outlook Calif Weekly: sec. Calif. Outlook; sec. fin. com. Roosevelt Pregt. Repub Lg. of Cal.
  - Poosevelt Club of Sacramento Co. - Saeramente 1912 -E. M. Sheehon Lessner Samule
  - Roosevelt, Theodore - 1910-1919Pres. U.S. - most are copies-orgs. w/ J. Lissner Family; contrib. ed. Outlook N.Y. - Kausas City Star secs. = Miss S. M. Striekes Frank Harper, Elbert E. Martin &? Geo Emlen Roosevelt
  - Roosevelt Memorial Assoc. - L.A. 1919s. * Marshall Stunson chairman. So. Calif.
  - Roosevelt Memorial Com. - L.A. 1919s. z Otto J. Zahn, sec.
  - Roosevelt Progressive Republican League of L.A. Co. - L.A. 1912 & n.d.Freg. s. Lee C. Gafes, pres.; Frank S. Hutton, sec.; by see F. E. Woodley, chairman finance com.
  - Roosevelt Progressive Club of Riverside Co. - Riverside 1912s. A. Hebet Winder, s.
  - Rose, H. H. - L.A. 1913candidate for may or signature ptd or stamped
  - Rose, H. H. Campaign Com. - L.A. 1913ptd. John Luckenbach, chairman.
  - Roseberry, Louis H. - Santa Barbara 1908-14atty, Calif Sena chairman. com. on Pub. Health & Guarantine; attg. trust dept, L.A. Security Trust & Savings Bank
  - Rosenwald, Julius - Chicago 1911with Sears, Roebuck & Co. exec offices
  - Rothschild, Nonnie - S.F. 1911Repub. St. Cent. Com.
  - Rowe, L.S. - Philadelphia 1911, 12, 15ch. of Pa. pres Amer Acad. of Polif. & Soc. Science
  - Rubinow, I. M. - N.Y. 1917exec. sec. American Medical Assoc., (1)
  - Runckel, Chris - Niles, Calif. 1911prep. Washington Press
  - * Russell, Charles Edward - Wn. D.C. 1913, 15, 19journalist & socialist
  - Rutherford, Wallace - Napa 1911, 16sec. Napa Co. Repub Cent. Com. pres. League of Calif. Municipalities
  - Ryan, Daniel A. - S.F. 1907, 11atty Cal. Rep. Cent. Com. dut or pres. Roosevelt Progressive Republican League
  - Rowan, R.A. & Co. - L.A. 1910 - 13, 15 - 18, 20real est brokers s. P.D. Rowan, treas.; R.A. Rowan, pres.; S.R. Lewis, v.p.; George W. Bliss, mgr. bond dept. & others (see folder)
  - Rowell, Chester H. - Fresno 1907, 08, 10, 11 - 13, 14 15 - 21Fresno Republican Publ. Co. - Fresno Morning Republican, Fresno Weekly Rep Lincoln - Roosevelt Republican League (Cal) sec.; cmmr. - Panama - Pacific Internat'l Exposition Cmm. Sadie Roberts = sec Rowell Progressive Club of S.F. (candidate for office 1914) ed. & mgr. Fresno Republican
  - Sackett, George L. - Sacramento 1911sec. State Text-Book Com. - Dept. Pub. Instruction
  - Sacramento Bee - Sacramento 1911s. William A. Lawson - assoc. editor
  - Sacramento, Hotel - Sacramento 1916, 12s. R. M. Bettens, W. H. Hanley
  - * Sacramento Co. Repue Cent. Com. - Sacramento 1912s. F.F. Canon, sec.
  - Saint Francis Hotel - S.F. 1915-17s. J.H. McCallough, off Mgr.; * Charles Baad, off. my
  - Saint Louis Public Service Cmm. - St. Louis, Mo. 1912s. J.E. Allison cmmr., chief engr.
  - Sale, L.D. - L.A. 1912 &pres. Western Wholesale Drug Co.
  - Salzman, Maurice - L.A. 1913,atty
  - Samuels, George - Oakland 1910, 13judge Oakland Police Court
  - * San Benito Co. Repub. Cent. Com. - Hollister 1912s. A.D. Shaw mgr. S.B. Advance
  - Sanders, Frederic W. - L.A. 1915, 16author: Reorg-of Our Schools
  - San Francisco Convention LG. - S.F. 1911s Felton Taylor, exec. sec.
  - * San Francisco Co. Repub. Cent. Com. - S.F. 1912s. * Philip Bancroft, sec.
  - San Francisco Supervisors BD - S.F. 1912s. J.S. Dunnigan, clerk
  - * San Joaquin Co. Repub. Cent. Com. - Stockton 1912s. C.L. Neumiller, s. W. H. Briggs, mgr. of HQ
  - * San Luis Obispo Co. Repub. Cent. Com. - S. Luis Obispo 1910, 12s. & L.A. Enos, chrmn.
  - * San Mateo Co. Repub. Cent. Com. - Redwood City 1912s. A.L. Lowe, sec.
  - San Pedro L-R Repub. Lg. - San pedro 1908s. R.L.Angell, sec. s. Henry Baly & J.H. Powers v. p s
  - * Santa Barbara Co. Repub Cent. Com. - Sta. Barbara 1910, 12s. J.L. Hurlbut, chrmn.; s. C.A. Hunt, Co. Clk.
  - Santa Clara Co. Repub Cent. Com. - San Jose 1912s. L.D. Bohnett, * W.A Be
  - Santa Cruz Co. Repub. Cent. Com. - Wastonville 1912s. E.E. Luther
  - Shapiro, Aaron - S.F. 1919atty
  - Challenberger, Margaret E. - Saeramento 1915Cal. Bd. Educ. - cmmr. Elementary Schools
  - Schaller, Albert - St. Paul, Miun. 1906atty, (1)
  - Scharrenberg, Paul - S.F. 1915, 19, 21sec.-tieas. Calif St. Fed. of Labor sec. Calif. Immigration & Housing Cmm.
  - * Scherer, James A.B. - Pasadena 1911-13, 15, 17, 19, 20pres. Throop Poly Inot. (also called Throop Inst., Throop College of Tech.) sec. Iuga Howard
  - Scherfee, Mis. James F. - L.A. 1913, 15pres Outlook Club, Outlook Assoc
  - * Schroeter, Ernest U. - Chicago 1912, 13Progressive Nat'l Com. atty
  - * Schweitzer, D.A. - L.A. 1913, 17, 18atty of Schweitzer & Hutton chairman. L.A. Co. Repub. Cent. Com.
  - Scott, James B. - Wn., D.C. 1911?Catnegie Endowment for Internatl Peace
  - Scott, Joseph - L.A. 1912, 14, 18, 19 n.d.atty 5 com. on schools L.A. Freeholders
  - Sears, Chatles N. - Bakers field 1910dumn.? Keth Co. Repub. Cent. Com.
  - Sears, William H. - Chillicothe, O. 1916, 17atty
  - Seattle Chamber of Commerce - Seattle, Wn. 1921s. Robert S. Boyns, pres.
  - Seavey, C. L. - Saeramento 1920mem. St. Bd. of Control Common Coaneil
  - Sehon, John L. - San Diego 1911supt. Dept. of Police, Health & Morals
  - * Seclenfreuno, A.B. - Chicago 1920sec. Indep. Ord. of B'nai B'rith
  - * Security Savings Bank - L.A. 1910, 11s. W.M. Caswell asst. sec., J.O. Griffin asst. sec.
  - Security Trust & Savines Bank - L.A. 1915-17s. Chas. H. Toll, v. p., * W.M. Caswell asst. sec.; s. G.W. Gastlin mgr. safe deposit dept.; R.M. Hardacre asst. cashier s M.S. Hellman, v.p
  - Seeley, Roy C., Co. - L.A. 1915, 20s. Charles Hinckley, J.N. Mills
  - Segnogram Publ. Co. - L.A. 1908s. * W. Eluro Reavis, sec
  - Shasta Co. Progressive Lg. - Redding 1912E.E. Todd, sec.
  - Shenk, J.W., (Sr.) - L.A. 1910, 12, 13City Atty
  - Sherman, Fical W. - Sta. Barbara 1911publt. Sta. Barbura Independent
  - Shinn, Charles H. - Northfork, Madera Co. 1911, 12, 13, 15, 16conservationist and writer
  - Short Ballot Organization - 1910, 12s. H.S. Gilbertson, asst. sec.
    SEE ALSO Natl Short Ballot Organization
  - Shortridge, Samuel M. - S.F. 1919-21atty, U.S. Sen. (Cal.)
  - Shoup, Paul - L.A. 1911, 12, 16, 18v.p. Pacific Electric Railway Co. & pres. (later pres. of Southern Pacific) v.p. Southern Pacific
  - Sierra Club - S.F. 1911 - 13, 16, 17, 21s. * William E. Colby see chrmn. & mgr. outing com.; * William F. Bade, Stanford Prof. editer; * Joseph N. Le Conte, outg. com. & pres. s. P.S. Bernays, see. So sect.; Charles J. Fox (L.A.) - chrmn. exec. com
  - Sierra Co. Repub Cent. Com. - Downieville 1912s. Henry E. Quigley, County Clk.
  - Simons, Grace C. (Mrs Seward C.) - S. Pasadena 1912, 15
  - Simons, James J. - L.A. 1911L.A. (off)
  - Simons, Seward C. - S Paradena 1912, 15, 16, 19sec. Munic Lg. of L.A.
  - Simpson, E. S. - S. F. 1908, 09mg. ed. S.F. Call
  - Sims, Edwin W. Chicago 1912sec. Natl Roosevelt Com., (1)
  - Sinclair, Upton - Pasadena 1917, (1)
  - Singletax, Provisional Natl Com. - Cincinnati, Ohio 1916s. Daniel Kiefer, chrmn.
  - Single Tax Lg. - L.A. 1921st. George A. Briggs, mgr.
  - Sinsheimer, Paul A. - S.F., 14, 1915, 16, 18, 19Calif. R R Cmm. boud expem asst. to pres., v.p. Union Trust Co.
  - Siskiyou Co Repub Cent. Com. - Yreka 1912s. L.F. Coburn, sec. s. W. J. Neilon, Co. Clk.
  - Slauson, James - L.A. 1910, 11 & n.d.pres. L.A. Chamber of Commerce
  - * Sloane, W.A. - San Diego 1907, 08, 10-12, 18, 20atty, chairman. exee. Com. San Diego Co. L-R Repub. Co., judge Superior Ct.; assoc. justice Calif. Supreme Ct.
  - Sloss, M.C. - S.F. 1910, 11assoc. justice Calif Supreme Ct. of Ste. Barbara
  - Smith, Edwin F, - Chicago 1912?at convention
  - Smith, Mary E. - L.A. 1913see to? polit. org.
  - Smith, Samuel Barnes - L.A. 1911, 13, 18 - 20El Centro atty
  - Smith, W. Clifford - Long Beach 1910 - 12sec. Long Beach Repub. Cl. sec - treas. Long Beach L-R Repub. Cl.
  - Snowden, J. W. - L.A. 1915L.A. City Council chrmn., Public Safety
  - Solano Co. Repub Cent Com. - Fairfield 1912s. G.G. Holliday, Co. Clk.
  - Sonoma Co Repub. Cent. Com. - Santa Rosa 1912s. Ira D. Pyle, sec. s. Rolfe L. Thompson, pres. Sta. Rosa Roosevelt Org.
  - So. Calif. Civil Service Lg - L.A. 1920s. Francis B. Kellogg
  - So. Calif. Edison Co. - L.A. 1911, 13, 14s. C.S. Walton, dist. agt. (Pasadena)
  - So. Calif. State Hospital - Patton 1921s. * John A. Reily, med. supt.
  - * Southern Pacific Co. - L.A. & S.F. 1912, 15, 16, 17
  - Southwest Museum - L.A. 1913s. * Charles F. Lummis, sec.
  - Southwest Society - L.A. 1913s. Charles F. Lummis, sec.
  - Southwestern Home Telephone Co. - Redlands, 1911s. Charles A. Rolfe, v.p.
  - Southwestern University - L.A. 1916, 1920s. Arthur S. Abbott, dean of law school & ed. Southwestern Law Review; s. Rollin L. McNitt, dean acting
  - Spalding, W.A. - L.A. 1910, 11, 13L.A. Civil Service
  - Spokane Pub. Utils. Dept. - Spokane, Wn. 1912s. C.M. Fassett, cmmt.
  - * Spreckels, Rudolph - S.F. 1907-09, 11, 17, 202 by sec.
  - Squire, F.C. - L.A. 1913asst. engr. San Pedro, L.A. & Salt Lk. RR Co.
  - Staats, William R. Co. - Pasadena 1912, 13, 15s. F.H. Heydenreich s. Lloyd R. Maey, see; Frank C. Mouree, v-p.
  - Stahlnecker, P.S. - Wm D.C. 1917?sec to Gifford Panchat
  - Standard Biscuit Co. - S.F. 1911s. Sam Jacoby
  - Standard Oil Co. - L.A. 1921s. D.F. Martin
  - Standish, Miles - S.F. 1910, 12Staudish - Hickey Timber Co
  - Stanislaus Co. Repus. Cent. Com. - Modeste 1910, 12s. G.H. Bertram, chrmn.; s. Hugh Benson, Co. clk., s. W.H. Langden, chrmn.
  - Stebbins, Tracy N. - L.A. 1912Stebbins Laud Co.
  - Steele, R.D. - L.A. 1919sec.-treas. Internatl Packing Corp.
  - Steigmeyer, Frederick W. - Westhaven, Fresue Co. 1919
  - Steffens, Lincoln - N.Y. 1912 & n.d.poet
  - Stephens, Albert Lee - L.A. 1914, 15 & n.d.City Atty
  - Stephens (Wm. D.) Congressional Club - L.A. 1914
  - Stephens-For-Congress Repub. Club - L.A. 1916
  - Stephens For Governor Club - L.A. 1918s. Mary E. Smith, sec.
  - Stephenson, T.E. - Santa Aua 1916assoc. ed. Register Publg. Co.
  - Stern, Charles F. - S.F. 1920, 21supt. of banks Calif St. Banking Dept.
  - Stetson, A.L. - L.A. 1911, 12, 13pres. Stetson, Barret Co.
  - Stevenson, Walter R. - L.A. 1916, 17, 19City Club of L.A sec.
  - Stetson, John W. - Oakland 1910-12, 18, 19Calif. Senate pres. Roosevelt Progressive Repub. Lg. of Calif, atty
  - Stilson, Fielding S. - L.A. 1907, 11real est Co. owner
  - Stimson, Marshall - L.A. 1907, 10 - 13atty, ? cmmr Panama - Pacific Exp sec. Harvard Club of So. Calif.
  - Stone, George - S.F. 1908chairman. Repub. St. Cent. Com. of Calif
  - * Stone, George Whitefield - Santa Cruz 1912, 13, 15may of Calif. St. Bd. of Educ. chairman. retirement salary fund com.
  - State (Calif) Compensation Insurance Fund - S.F. 1915, 17-21 n.d.s. C.W. Fellows 1915, 17, 18, 19, 20mgr.; E.R. Welch, 1917, 18, n.d.supt. claim dept.; J.R. Cornwell 1918asst. underwriter; s. Daniel W. Batbank, 1918counsel; G.W. Linch 1919supt. under wr. dept. s. H.B. Humphrey, 1920L.A. branch mgr.; S.L. Leman, 1920payroll dept.; s. Frank J. Creede, 1920atty; Grove J. Fink, 1920fen. sec.; s. L. Johnson, 1920, 21underwriter; H. Kress, 1920, 21underwriter; s. R. W. Pendergast, 1921asst. sec.
  - Stephens, William D. - L.A. Wn. O.C. 1911-16, 17 - 19U.S. House of Reps.; A. Mande Robinson 1911sec.; com. on census, com. on naval affrs.; Gov. of Calif. 1917;John C. McFarland, 1917exec. sec.; Martin C. Madsen, 1919pvt. sec.
  - * Straus, Nathan - Palestine Advancement Soc. - L.A. 1915s Henry Fram, sec.
  - * Strother, E. French - Sacramento 1911, 12?sec. of Albert I. Wallac
  - * Sullivan, Mark - N.Y. 1908, 15 - 17, 19, 20et. Collier's Nat'l Weekly
  - Summerfield, J.W. - L.A. 1921judge Superior Ct.
  - Survey - N.Y. 1915s. J.P. Heaton, bw. mgr.
  - Sutherland, W.A. - Sacramento 1911, 12(Fresno) atty, Calif. Assb.
  - Suzzalo, Henry - Seattle, Wn. 1919pres. U. of Wn.
  - Swing, Phil D. - El Centre 1912, 13, 15 - 20law partner of J. M. Eshleman; D. A. Imperial Co.; chf counsel Imperial Imig. Dist.; judge superior cf.
  - Taft, Fred H. L.A. 1910, 11, 15, 16atty - judge Super Cl. Reg. (Juvenile)
  - Taft, William H. - Wn. D.C. 1908See of War U. S. Pres. 1. L.S. & 1 typed 2 by Fred. W. Carpenter, pvt sec.
  - Taggart, Clarence M. - L.A. 1912L.A. City Tax & Licence Collector
  - Tarbell, Ida M. - N.Y. 1911, 12American Magazine
  - Tax Assoc. of Alameda Co. - Oakland 1915s. E.W. Williams
  - Taylor, B. Grant - San Jose 1910-13, 15atty, clk., Calif Supreme Ct
  - Taylor, Edward [R.] - Alameda 1907mayor
  - Teague, Charles Collins - Santa Paula 1912, 13
  - Tehama Co. Repus. Cent. Com - Red Bluff 1912F.A. Kahn, sec. s. Marshall Demotte
  - Telephony - Chicago 1911Am. Telephone Journal s. F.H.Reed
  - Telle, William - L.A. 1910, 11, 12, 21
  - Thelen, Max - S.F. 1911-15, 17, 19atty & cmmr. Calif. R R Comm a pres.; pres. Natl Assoc. of Ry. Commos; U.S. R R Admin. chrmn., Pub. Sec.
  - Thomas, Charles W., Jr. - Sacramento 1915, 16adj. gen. Military Dept. of Calif
  - Thomas, W.H. - Santa Ana 1912sec. Orange Co. Repub. Cent. Com.
  - Thomas, W.R. - Las Vega. Neo. 1912
  - Thompson, C. Bertrand - Boston 1915org. sec. of Boston - 1915
  - Thompson, Joseph O. - Birmingham, Ala. 1918candidate for Congress
  - Thompson, Newton W. - L.A., Sacramento 1910, 11, 13, 15Calif. Senate Pres. prefer
  - Thompson, Rolfe L. - Santa Rosa 1910-12atty
  - Thompson, William Boyce - N.Y. 1920chrmn., Natl ways & means com. Repub. Natl.
  - Thum, William - Pasadena 1911, 15, 20
  - * Title Insurance & Trust Co. - L.A. 1903, 19, 20s. O. P. Clark, 1903sec.; Erle M. Leaf, trust counsel 1919, 20;W. D. Smalley? escrow; s. Otis H. Castle, acting trust counsel; R. K. Snow, asst. trust offr.
  - ? Todd, Helen M. - S.F. 1911, 12
  - ? Toplitz, Melville S. - S.F. 1910, 11, 20
  - ? Toplitzky, Joe - L.A. 1917real est., (1)
  - Townshend, Sidney P. - Chestertown, Md, treas. Kent Co., Md., Roosevelt Com.
  - Traeger, William I. - L.A. 1921county sheriff, (1)
  - Treasury Dept. (U.S.) - L.A. 1918Div. of Loans & Currency s. Harold Janss, dir. pub.; L.A. 1921U.S Customs Service s. John B. Elliett, collector
  - Treat, Charles H. - L.A. 1911, 15, (2)
  - Tuberculosis, Calif. Assn. for Study & Prevention of - L.A. 1915s. Edith L. M. Tate exec. sec.
  - Tulare Co. Repub. Cent. Com. - Visalia 1912s. Avon M. Coburn, Co. Clk; s. James M. Burke, chrmn.
  - Tyrrell, Frank G. - L.A. 1906, 07, 10, 11, 15atty, counsel Nat'l Life Ins. & Thomas K. Kase
  - Union Bank & Trust Co. - L.A. 1918s. J.W. Lewis, asst. cashier & trust offr. s. * A. L. Lathrep, trust offr.
  - Union League Club - L.A. 1911, 13, 18ptd. M.S. Gregory, sec.; s. B.M. Tuttle, asst. sec. & mgr.; D.C. Casselman, pres.
  - U.S. Shipping Bd. - Wn., D.C. 1917, 18s. George E. Oller, off. mgr.
  - U'Ren, William S. - Oregon City, Ore. 1910socialist
  - * Uhl, Adolph - S.F. 1910 - 12 & n.d.(list) treas. Calif. Repub. St. Cent. Com Uhl Bros.
  - * U'Ren, Milton T. - S.F. 1910 - 12, 15atty sec. Dueet Legis Lg. of Calif.; sec. Committee on Conservation
  - Verrill, Charles H. - Wn. D.C. 1918Internat'l Assoc. of Indus. Acc. Bds. & Cmms. sec. com. on statistics & compensation ins. cost
  - Voorhees, George E. Jr. - Santa Barbara 1912
  - Votes For Women Club - L.A. 1911, n.d.s. Clara Shortridge Foltz, pres. s. Mary E. Foy, sec.
  - Vroman, James P. - L.A. 1911
  - * Walcott, E.A. - S.F. see * Commonwealth Club of Calif, exec. sec.
  - Walker, George S. - S.F. 1911, 15, 16Cal. Bldg & Loan Cmmr.
  - Wallace, Frank S. - Pasadena 1911, 12, 17
  - Wallace, William H. - L.A. 1921exec. sec. Y.M.C.A. Central Branch, (1)
  - * Wanamaker, R.M. - Columbus, O. 1915judge Ohio Supreme Ct.
  - * Ward, Edward J. - Madison, Wisc. 1911advisor U. of Wisc., Extension Div., Dept. of Gen. Info & Welfare Civic & Social Center Dev
  - Wardrop, G.D. - N.Y. 1913Outlook, off. of T. Roosevelt ?
  - Warren, Alan I. - L.A. 1911? League of Justice
  - Washington State Pub. Service Cmm. - Olympia, Wn. 1912s. George A. Lee, chairman.
  - Wallace, Albert J. - S.F. 1910-13, 16Calif. Lt. Gov.; Traders Oil Co. (L.A.); Olive Nettleton, steve
  - Watchorn, Robert - L.A. 1911, 12treas. & asst. to pres. Union Oil Co. of Calif
  - Watrous, Richard B. -? Wn. D.C. 1912, 13, 15 & n.d.sec. American Civic Assoc.
  - Watson, L.A. - L.A. 1912grand chancellor Calif. Knights of Pythia
  - Watt, Rolla Vernon. - S.F. 1907, 15, 18mgr. Royal Ins. Co. off John T. Fogarily, asst. mgr.
  - Wayside Press - L.A. 1917s. [A. M. Dunn], pres.
  - * Webb, U.S. - S.F. 1917-20atty, Calif. Atty Gen., Frank English = dep.
  - * Weil, A. Lee - Pittsburgh, Pa. 1917, 19atty
  - ? Weller, Dana R. - L.A. 1919judge Superior Ct.
  - ? West, George P. - S.F. 1912S.F. Bulletin
  - * ** Weinstock, Harris - Sacramento S.F. 1907, 08, 10-12, 15, 17, 18, 20, 21pres. Weinstock, Lubin & Co.,? Weinstock Nichols Co. Weinstock - Nichols Co.; St. Market Dir. Calif. Cmm. Market
  - West Publg. Co. - St. Paul, Minn. 1905, 06, 19, 2s. Wm. L. West, sec. s. W.G. Fordyce, William L. Strong, auditor
  - * Western Union Telegraph Co. - L.A. 1906, 11, 12, 16, 19s. R.H. Miller, 1906L.A. mgr.; J.M. Green, mgr. Sacramento 1911;L.A. City supt. 1920s. G.A. Lawrence, mgr. L.A. 1912, 16;H.F. Dodge 1912S.F. div. com'l sup't. s. C.E. House - L.A. mgr. credits & collections 1919
  - * Western Wholesale Drug Co. - L.A. 1913, 15, 17s. L. Schuff, v-p.; E.A. Talbot
  - * Westover, Myron - L.A. 1912, 15, 16, 19atty dep. City Atty Calif. RR. Cmm. examiner
  - * Wheeler, Benjamin Ide Barkeley 1907, 08, 11, 12pres. U of Calif Farnham P. Griffulus, ser.
  - Wheeler, Charles S. - S.F. 1911, 12, 18, 20, 24atty (sec. = C.H. McDouagh)
  - Wheeler, Henry O. Jr. - L.A. 1911, 15, 17-19atty, 1st U. WWI
  - Wheeler, William R. - S.F. 1913, 14Chamber of Commerce
  - * Wheeler Brothers and Pierce, Inc. - L.A. 1915-20ins agents s. D.W. Pierce, M. Rardin
  - * Whitaker, C.N. -? Monrovia 1908, 10 - 12(alot of correspondence); ? El Monte Gazette Weekly Recorder, (Loomis, Cal.) = Loomis Recorder, ed.? Calif. St. Bd. of Control, Steward Napa State Hospital
  - * White, W.O. - Ukiah 1910 - 12see. Mendocino Co. Repub. Cent. Co. owner & ed. Ukiah Republican Press
  - * Whitlock, Brand - Toledo (? Ohio) 1908, (1)
  - * Wiggins, Frank - L.A. see L.A. Chamber of Commerce & L.A. Convention League
  - * Wilbur, Curtis D. - L.A. 1910, 18, 20judge superior of assoc. justice Calif. Supreme Cf.
  - Wilcox, Delos F. - N.Y. 1910, 11, 15N.Y. Sf. Pub. Serv. Cmm. clif. Bureau of Franchises
  - * White, William Allen - Emporia, Kas. 1912, 13, 15 - 20ed. & owner Emporica Gazette W.E. Hughes, mgr.
  - Wilkinson, S. W. & Co. - L. A. 1912, 13, 15 - 20s. James W. Wilkinson real estate
  - Will, Arthur P. - L.A. 1911 - 13, 15, 16, 20editor in chief L.D. Powell Co.; chief Calif. Legis Counsel Bureau (much of it undated, kept in orig. order material (u.d.) to Fischer at en 1912?
  - Willard, C. D. - L.A. 1907 - 13sec. Municipal Lg. of L.A.
  - Williams, Churchill - Philadelphia 1914(1)? Saturday Evening Post, Curtis Publg
  - Williams, Edgar - Redlands 1912, 13, 16, 17, 19, 20, 21Redlands Daily Review pres. Calif. St. Civil Service Cmm.
  - Williams, Thomas S. -S.F. 1913Bd. of St. (Calif) Harbor Cmm
  - Williams, W. R. -S.F. Sacramento 1910, 11, 16, 19Calif. St. Treas.; supt. of banks, Calif. St. Banking Dept.; Bank of Italy
  - Williams Law & Collection Agency - L.A. 1904s. C.B. Williams to Hilda G. & George Humphries
  - Williamson, C.C. - N.Y. 1915(1) librarian N.Y. Public Lib. - Municipal Ref. Branch
  - Wilton Foto Film Service -L.A. 1918(1) s. Frank S. Wilton (see also Exactus)
  - Windham, C.H. - Long Beach 1911(1) mayor
  - Wing, Adeline Stearns (Mrs. Horace B.) - L.A. 1910
  - ?Winship, Addison L. -Boston 1911civic see. Boston City Club
  - Wisconsin, Railroad Cmm. of - Madison, Wisc. 1911, 12s. Halford Emekson
  - * Wise, Stephen S.-N.Y. 1915N.Y. Free Synagogue
  - Woman Citizen- N.Y. 1920(1) s. * Rose Young - editor
  - Wood, Edward Randolph - Philadelphia 1915, 161st v.p. Phila Bd. of Trade
  - Woodhead, Field & Co. -S.F. 1915s. J. Montague, asst. Cashier; Sunset Magazine
  - Woodley, Frank E.-L.A. 1912 13, 15, 21, n.dsec. Reliance Co. Calif Assb., L.A. Bd. of Supervisors
  - Woodman, Frederic T. -L.A. 1917mayor, (1)
  - Woods, James - S.F. 1914gen. mgr. Hotel St. Francis
  - Woolwine, Clare - L.A. 1921atty, (1)
  - * Woolwine, Thomas Lee - L.A. 1916, 20L.A.Co. D.A. R. Starbuch, sec.
  - * Works, John Downey - L.A. 1908, 10-12atty L.A. City Charter, column. com. of Three; U.S. Senate
  - * Woodruff, Clinton Rogers - Philadelphia 1908, 10-20see. Nat'l Municipal Lg.; editor Natl Municipal Review; atty ( R.T. Sheets? see to CRW)
  - Works, Lewis R. - L.A. 1908, 11, 12, 13asst. City atty
  - Wright, Charles F. - Mayfield, Calif. 1917atty
  - Wright, Purd B. - L.A. 1910, 11librarian
  - Wright-Callender-Andrews Co. - L.A. 1913, 17s. A.C. Mortis, mgr. s. A.G. Davenport, business leasing dept.; B.E. Percival, rental dept. s. C.A. Williamson
  - Wyllie, G.W. - Dinuba, Calif. 1910, 17Karnak Vineyard, Calif. Asst
  - Yolo Co Repub. Cent. Com. - Woodland 1912s. D.E.Jacobs, sec.
  - Yonkers Bureau of Municipal Research, Inc. - Yonker, W.Y. 1919,Stephen J. Patte sec.
  - Young, Milton K. - L.A. 1919, 21lawyer
  - Young, R. H. - Long Beach 1911, 12, 16, 18-20
  - ?Zahn, Otto J. - L.A. 1910, (1)